Yes, Judith, I did deduct $30
from your child-support check this month.
Because I paid for Jake's haircut.
Yes, it is usually $9, but he wanted
to go someplace without hobbyhorses.
I know he's never gonna win
any beauty contests, but he is our son.
Look, I've got a patient. I gotta go.
Sorry you had to hear that.
That's, uh... That's my ex-wife.
Beyotch.
- Hello, Mrs. Honeycutt. I'm Dr. Harper.
- Doctor.
Okay, so you are having spasms
in your lower back?
Yeah, it's awful.
Some days I can't even get out of bed.
- Oh, I know how that is.
- You have back problems too?
No.
Why don't you lie face down?
We'll see if we can locate the problem.
I've tried everything.
Acupuncture, yoga, shiatsu.
Nothing seems to work.
Not surprised. Those Eastern practices
are mostly hooey.
Modern chiropractic, on the other hand,
is built on over 50 years of solid science.
Okay, let's take a look
at what we've got here.
- Okay. Now, is this too much pressure?
- No.
- Okay, how about this?
Okay. Now, is this
where the spasms occur?
- A little lower.
- Okay.
- Here?
- Ahh, lower.
- Aww! Oh.
- Am I hurting you?
- No. God, no.
Nobody's touched me like this
since my husband died.
Oh, um, I'm so sorry. Um...
How long has it been since...
That long, huh?
Oh, my. It's, uh, pretty sensitive here.
Harder.
Oh. Okay, no problem. Um.
So just out of curiosity,
how did you find me?
A referral? My website?
Or the flyers at the Mongolian barbecue
across the street?
Shut up and rub.
Uh, I'm not technically rubbing.
- Whoa, Nelly.
Oh! Don't stop.
I'm not stopping.
Oh, spank me.
I'm... I'm sorry?
Spank my lonely ass!
What?
Do it, bitch!
Yes, Dr. Harper! Yes!
Oh, God, yes!
Okay, let's take a look at the schedule.
See what the rest
of the afternoon looks like.
Oh, that's not too bad.
So how are you liking
your first day at work here?
Thank you, Dr. Harper.
Uh, you are most welcome.
And remember, alternating an ice pack
with a, uh, a heating pad...
...is very helpful for spasming.
- I'd like to make another appointment.
- Oh, sure, sure.
What were you thinking?
Maybe next week or?
- Tonight.
- To... Uh...
Tonight? Oh, gloriosky.
- Well, we, uh, we close up at 5...
- So I can expect you at my place at 9.
Oh, gee, uh, I don't do house calls.
Per se.
See you at 9.
Uh... Some patients pay in cash.
Their insurance, uh,
won't cover chiropractic.
Part of our ongoing healthcare crisis.
Tragic, really.
Uh, by the way,
you are doing one heck of a job.
In fact, here's a little something for you.
Just because your smile
lights up the place.
You know what? Let's sweeten the pot.
Um, can you give me 10 back?
Not a problem.
Can't put a price on a smile.
- I like the new look.
- Thanks.
It's fashion forward.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
It's what the guy who cut my hair said.
He also said it was fun and fabulous.
Really?
Yeah. And he invited Dad to a party.
I didn't go.
It's just nice to be asked.
So why'd you decide to abandon
your classic cereal-bowl coif?
What's a coif?
- You can't glean it from the context?
- What's "glean"?
Why'd you change your freaking hair?
My new girlfriend wanted me to.
If your girlfriend wanted you
to jump off a bridge, would you?
If she put her tongue in my mouth
when she asked me, yeah.
I can't blame you. I bought a woman
a car for the same reason.
She put her tongue in your mouth?
Sure, let's say "mouth."
Can we get the check, please?
Hey, why don't you let me get this one?
Really? Not gonna go
for the world record?
- What?
- One thousand six hundred...
...and forty-seven meals in a row where
you haven't taken out your Velcro wallet.
- You were counting?
- Am I close?
Nevertheless, I'm paying.
Smell that? The air coming out
of your father's wallet...
...has been in there
since before you were born.
Very funny.
- Thank you.
- Wait, wait.
Nobody is gonna believe this.
For God's sake.
Hey, isn't that Chelsea's friend Gail?
Oh, yeah.
- Wonder if I should say hello.
- I wouldn't mind.
Finish paying the check, you weasel.
As long as you got your wallet out,
I could use new sneaks.
Hm. Oh.
Sure.
Are you dying?
- Charlie.
- Oh, hi, Gail.
- Great to see you.
- How have you been?
Pretty good. You?
Well, you know.
Yeah, I'm sorry to hear
about you and Chelsea.
Way it goes.
Win some, lose some, start having
liquor delivered to your house...
...so you don't have to put on pants.
If it's any consolation,
I know how you feel.
I'm still not over my breakup.
But I'm not much of a drinker, so cheers.
Have you, um... Have you seen Chelsea?
Yeah. Actually, I had dinner
with her and...
We had dinner just the other night.
- Her and Brad?
- Yeah, come to think of it, he was there.
- Sounds like they're an item now, eh?
- I guess.
You guess?
What do you want?
They're in Mexico for the weekend.
Mexico. Nice. I went there with her once.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no. It's fine.
We had a great time. In fact,
when we got back, I bought her a car.
Yeah, she told me.
Eww.
Listen, I gotta go.
But if you ever wanna talk...
Oh, thank you.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
For the last time, I am not dying
and I'm not sick. Everything's fine.
Okay, I got it.
But you can understand
my skepticism, right?
I really don't see
why I shouldn't ask her out.
Seriously? The woman
is Chelsea's best friend.
So? She's single. I'm single.
She's lonely. I'm lonely.
She's gorgeous. I'm well above average.
- I'm just saying it's a bad idea.
- I never said it wasn't a bad idea.
I said, I don't know why I shouldn't do it.
- What is that?
- It's a portable massage table.
So you're giving rub-and-tugs
on the pier now?
No. No, I am a licensed professional.
And I will not stand here
and be accused of unethical behavior.
I mean, just because you have
no moral compass doesn't mean I don't.
And while, yes, that's a triple negative...
...it, nevertheless, defines me as the man
for whom I am aiming to be.
What the hell are you talking about?
I am just trying to augment my income
by seeing clients in their homes...
...thus, alleviating them
of the added stress of commuting.
Not to mention speed bumps
and pot holes...
...of which, as you know,
can jostle the spine.
Wow, guy picks up one $30 check
and he has a brain aneurysm.
Yeah?
Chelsea?
Hey, how are you?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down. Slow down.
Why are you crying?
Wait a minute, you're in Mexico?
Why on Earth are you in Mexico?
Oh, sure, Brad.
Oh, sweetie,
I'm sorry it's not working out.
Well, I love you and I miss you too.
When are you gonna be back?
Okay. Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
I can't wait.
All right. Bye-bye, sweetie.
I hope that smile is for me.
Uh...
Who else would it be for?
You ready for round two?
Well, um...
...yes and no.
- Is something wrong?
- Yeah.
While you were in the bathroom,
uh, Chelsea called.
Really?
Apparently, things didn't go well
in Mexico and she's coming home.
Oh, that's a shame.
Yeah.
Anyway, she wants to see me.
Said she loves me and misses me.
So one call and you're just
gonna go running back?
Uh, yeah.
Well, heh.
This is awkward.
Come on, you know how I feel about her.
I do.
So we should probably keep...
...what happened tonight
just between us, right?
Mum's the word. Zip the lip.
Lx-nay on the oggy-day yle-stay?
Of course.
You know...
...we could just pretend that you didn't
get the phone call for, like...
...another hour.
We could, couldn't we?
But wouldn't that be wrong?
I won't tell if you don't.
Ugh, I'm sorry, Gail.
I can't justify it to myself.
Okay.
Well, can I at least kiss you good night?
Sure.
On the other hand,
there's no arguing with a boner.
Let's see,
when Gail came over, it was 11:00 here...
...and midnight in Cabo.
When Chelsea called,
it was midnight here and 1:00 in Cabo.
So when I did Gail at 12:10,
Chelsea technically hadn't called yet.
Not my best work, but I can live with it.
- Hey.
Tough night, Bunky?
I'm a whore, Charlie.
Oh, don't be so hard on yourself.
Jake needed a haircut,
and you had no money.
What? No. No.
I took money to give a woman pleasure.
Wait a minute. You...
...gave a woman pleasure?
Oh, you have no idea
what powerful orgasms these hands...
...are capable of delivering.
No, I've always known that.
I just find it hard to believe...
...they could give them to other people.
Yeah, well, maybe this'll convince you.
- A woman gave you this?
- Uh-huh.
Right before she told me she was done
with me and I could show myself out.
Sounds like a dream date to me.
So, what's the problem?
How do I live with myself?
How did you live with yourself before?
By thinking I was better than you.
Now, after all these years,
I've descended to your level.
Oh, no, no, no.
I may have done
some questionable things...
...but I have never taken money for it.
That's not to say it wasn't offered.
And deservedly so.
Fine, I'm worse than you.
That's all I'm saying.
Well, I am going to take a shower
and try to wash the cheapness off me.
Better take some steel wool
and a cheese grater.
Hey, Alan.
Oh. Gail.
Hi.
Don't judge me, Pretty Woman.
- Uh, Charlie, I better get going.
- Right. Right.
So, uh, you and I are okay?
Yeah. I'm just sorry it has to end.
- Yeah, me too.
- Chelsea's a lucky girl.
You think so? You should tell her.
I mean, don't tell her.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
Thank you, Charlie.
- For what?
- Proving once again...
...that I am better than you.
Hey. Hey. I'm just a rascal.
You are a male prostitute.
That is a terribly hurtful thing to say.
So there we are in this beautiful
hotel room overlooking the ocean...
...and he's on the phone with his mother,
trying to help her download music.
- You're kidding.
- And I just sat there thinking:
"Charlie would never do this. Charlie
hates his mother with a blind passion."
Remember when you used to think
that was a bad thing?
And when Brad's not on the phone...
...he's telling me how much
I remind him of his mother.
I hope not while you were in bed.
Because that would reflect badly
on everybody.
You don't wanna know.
There's nothing to know.
You went to Mexico with another man...
...he talked about his mother in bed,
and you didn't have sex with him.
- Charlie...
- That's what happened. End of story.
I should never have let you go.
Well, sometimes you can't appreciate
what you've got...
...until you go to Mexico
and don't have sex with a mama's boy.
I'm sorry about Brad.
I know that hurt you.
Water under the bridge.
What you did, what I did, doesn't matter.
- What did you do?
- Doesn't matter.
Charlie, no secrets.
Please, can't I just have one?
Whatever it is, it doesn't matter.
We were separated.
All right, here goes.
I was having pizza
with Alan and Jake the other day.
By the way, Jake got a new haircut.
It's just fabulous.
Okay, well, you'll never guess
who was there getting takeout.
Your old buddy Gail.
Oh, my God, you didn't.
I didn't say I did, but good guess.
- I don't believe you.
- What?
We were separated. You were in Mexico.
But she's my best friend.
Yeah, well, I'd have to say
the jury's still out on that.
You are such a pig.
A... A... A pig who hates his mother.
Go to hell.
Oh, come on. It was 1:00 in Cabo.
Lower.
How about here?
Oh, yeah. That's how Mommy likes it.
Okay, you know what? I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
- What's wrong?
- I am a professional.
I studied chiropractic
for three years in Guadalajara.
That was with almost
no Spanish language skills...
...and a family of parasites
living in my colon.
And I did not go through all of that
to become some sort of G-spot Johnny.
Is that what you think you are?
Well, you're giving me money
and I'm giving you...
...what I'm giving you.
It just makes me feel cheap.
It's too much
like a business transaction.
Exactly.
How about we forget the money...
...and I'll show you something
I learned in Guadalajara?
What?
Oh, hey. Hi.
I'm sorry. I overreacted.
Yeah, you kind of did.
You're both single, you're both adults,
and you and I were separated.
Plus, you were honest with me,
so I'm willing to put it behind us.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
I love you so much.
I love you too.
Why don't I take you out for a nice lunch
and we'll catch up?
You wanna go out?
I'm a little hungry.
Aren't you a little hungry?
Gail's upstairs, isn't she?
Once again, we were separated
and I was vulnerable.
Just so we're on the same page, are we
together or am I allowed to go upstairs?
Damn.
Oh, how much madder could she get?
Okay, well, I think we're making good
progress with the back spasms.
- Thank you. I'll see you on Wednesday.
- Looking forward to it.
- And Mrs. Honeycutt?
- Yes?
If it's okay, I'd like to go back
to our original arrangement.
But you said it made you feel cheap.
What can I say? Turns out I am cheap.
Your call. Bye-bye.
Bye.
Ha, have I told you lately
that you are doing a great job?
Ha-ha-ha.
Because you are doing a great job.
In fact, I am gonna make you
employee of the month.
I want an adjustment.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Are you having back problems?
No, I want an adjustment
like you give her.
Oh, gee, I don't think
that would be appropriate.
All right,
then I want a raise and dental insurance.
Hop on the table.